Vengeance is the only justice.
River Runs Red is a thriller, crime film directed by Wes Miller.
When the son of a successful judge is killed by two police officers and the system sets them free, a hardened veteran detective finds some
incriminating files on the officers and the judge teams up with another mourning father to take the law into his own hands.
Charles Coleman, Sr., played by Taye Diggs.
Horace, played by John Cusack.
Javier, played by George López.
Von, played by Luke Hemsworth.
Rory, played by Gianni Capaldi.
Marilyn, played by Briana Evigan.
River Runs Red is a 2018 American thriller film written and directed by Wes
Miller and starring Taye Diggs, John Cusack and George Lopez.
The film explores themes of police, detective, murder.
The tone is intense.